<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">TestAdventure</string>
    <string name="new_game">NEW GAME</string>
    <string name="quit_game">QUIT GAME</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="choose_your_gender">Choose Your Gender</string>
    <string name="type_your_name">Type Your Name</string>
    <string name="hint">Your Name</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="choose_character_class">Choose Character Class</string>
    <string name="assassin">Assassin</string>
    <string name="mage">Mage</string>
    <string name="warrior">Warrior</string>
    <string name="new_game_after_dead">NEW GAME</string>
    <string name="checkpoint">CHECKPOINT</string>
    <string name="you_have_found_weapon">YOU HAVE FOUND WEAPON !</string>
    <string name="take">Take</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="hello_may_freind">Hello my friend</string>
    <string name="name">Name:</string>
    <string name="health_points">Health Points:</string>
    <string name="attack2">Attack:</string>
    <string name="agillity">Agillity:</string>
    <string name="strength">Strength:</string>
    <string name="intelligence">Intelligence:</string>
    <string name="class1">Class:</string>
    <string name="return1">Return</string>
    <string name="weapon_name">Weapon Name:</string>
    <string name="attack">Attack:</string>
    <string name="show_stats">UPDATE STATS</string>
    <string name="introduction">Example text</string>
    <!--Hi, My name is Mateusz and this is my firs mobile game. I wish you like it. Enjoy!-->
    <string name="gifavatar">TODO</string>
    <string name="try_to_fight">Try to fight</string>
    <string name="you_were_unexpectedlly_attacked">YOU WERE UNEXPECTEDLY ATTACKED!</string>
    <string name="UnexpectedAssault">TODO</string>
    <string name="czas_rusza_dalej">Time to move on</string>
    <string name="unikniecie_walki">THANKS TO YOUR CUNNING, YOU MANAGED TO AVOID THE FIGHT !</string>
    <string name="just_look_on_a_massacre">During your journey you saw a fight. Watch as other travelers are massacred by the creation unknown to you, you move on in the chosen direction.</string>
    <string name="strange_beast">The longer road has saved you from fighting bandits in the forest. Wandering through a quiet wetland, you have encountered an abomination that you have never known before. It was sitting on an isolated stone in the middle of the pool, staring at you with a blank look. Intuition told you that it is best to calmly retreat. You did as you thought. Being in a safe distance, you decided to look back for the last time, but when you turned back, the rest of the beast was empty.</string>
    <string name="good_end">Eventually, after a fierce battle, you managed to defeat the beast, pon return I am going to deal with the client - you thought. Today I got rid of the last living ancient creature. At least you thought so…</string>
    <string name="bad_end">Eventually, after a fierce battle, you did not manage to defeat the beast, disputing terror and terror on your land. Where the beast will rule for all time. At least it seemed so…</string>
    <string name="first_choice">-Hey you! - Hey you there! I am talking to you.. Get up, Garond broke you so hard. I told you to pay attention to words. Let me introduce myself: I am Greg. (All sore and bruised, you rise from the ground) - my name is… - I do not care what your name is! I know one thing, you are just a miserable slave and you have two choices. First I will sell you as a mercenary to Camp on the Rocky Shore or leave you unattended here to die as you try something sneaki again. Choose.</string>
    <string name="camp_on_rock_shore">A Camp on the Rocky Shore</string>
    <string name="try_to_get_out">Try to free yourself</string>
    <string name="gate">You made the right choice. I would not want to lose such valuable goods. (After that Greg brought you some poor clothes, a pile of old stale bread and a bowl of water. You do not remember anything. Who are you, who you were, or how you got on it fucking ship shackled! You have one goal. Wait until everything is quiet and try to escape from the camp somehow.) When I get a weapon? - You get aweapon! Ha that you all get killed when we sleep?! You will not get any weapons! - But how can I be a mercenary if I can not defend myself? - think of something! Ahhh the gate of the camp is already there! Only without any tricks, the gate guard is not the most patient person hehe. (You can see powerful gates through your eyes, and a single man standing by it. Does not look like someone you can play with). -My name is Thorus </string>
    <string name="be_calm">Without any tricks!</string>
    <string name="thief_the_key">Steal the Keys from the Gate</string>
    <string name="chaos_in_camp">(The first night when you could not fall asleep busy with reflections on the future, past and most importantly who you once were, it gave a powerful bang ! The camp was attacked! There was panic and chaos in one moment. It was your chance, your happy luck! You have to come up with a plan to escape, think, think…)</string>
    <string name="backdor">Exit the back door</string>
    <string name="armory">Go through the window to the armory (risky)</string>
    <string name="wait_in_house">Wait in the house</string>
    <string name="weapon_text">-I have the strange impression that I have used such a weapon before.. In addition, suspiciously pulsating in my hand… (In total, you have not thought about it) -Thanks to it, I can finally defend myself!!</string>
    <string name="hide_in_drawer">(You decided to wait in the house coward.. To make matters worse, you hid in the closet… seriously… there was no better hideout? When you waited so suddenly you heard disturbing sounds from the distance of the room ! What can it be you think.. what to do?)</string>
    <string name="check_this_out">You should check it out</string>
    <string name="lost_hp">(After a fierce battle, you finally won. And so you are surprised, that you are still alive.. However, it was not without losses. Due to the lack of a weapon, you lost your hand and you are overwhelmed with strange feelings and curses. You did not take the opponents weapon because it broke during the fight. However, the weapon is not my biggest concern - you thought. It is time to get out of here. Badly bruised, but alive you reached the edge of the forest near the village. No plan, no food. You decided to move further into the depths of the forest.)</string>
    <string name="to_the_forest">To the forest</string>
    <string name="win_fight">(After a fierce battle with the bandit, you finally won. And so you are surprised that you are still alive.. Surprisingly, the fact that you wield your weapon well did not escape and only thanks to it you did not suffer any major losses. It is time to get out of here. You have been all and well fed to the edge of the forest near the village. No plan, no food, but with weapons and determination. You decided to move further into the depths of the forest.)</string>
    <string name="baal_fight">(After a year and a half of wandering and searching for your own identity, you have developed your fighting skills and you have taken care of killing monsters on your behalf. Your next goal was a small dragon in the Rocky Mountains. You have dealt with it without a problem. Something was wrong. In one moment, the mighty body of the beast emerged from behind the mountains. Orshabaal. That is why the reward was high up … not a moment passed, Baal threw a piece of the mountain into you, which he nudged one hand with his paw…</string>
    <string name="dalej">further</string>
    <string name="orsh_bad">After one and a half years of wandering barely alive you got to the city, in which, however, you met another unpleasantness. Orshabaal, you have never seen this creature on your eyes, and now standing in front of you staring at you. In a moment darkness gripped you. The old curse let me know. However, you did fight. At one moment, Orhsh hits you with a boulder…</string>
    <string name="sneak_peak">(You did it!!! Thorus turned out to be an ordinary guard who sheds his skin three more times ;)In the evening .. in the evening I call it - you thought. Time passed, and you calmly waited until everyone was asleep to be able to put the plan into effect … Time has come. You have shackled the shackles quietly and you escaped unnoticed from the camp. By reaching the crossroads from afar you have noticed that the camp in which you last stayed was attacked. Ha tragedy - you thought. There is no time to lose, you have to move on.)</string>
    <string name="chooser">A bit further you came to the crossroads of roads. I have to choose two paths one leads to the forest and wetlands (long and hard crossing), and the other towards the mountains. What to choose?</string>
    <string name="to_the_mountains">In the mountains</string>
    <string name="mountain_death">During the crossing through the mountains, you encountered the Little Dragon. Fleeing, you fell into the abyss.</string>
    <string name="camp_death">At the back of the hut, one of the bandits was waiting for the survivors. He cut your head with a quick move.</string>
    <string name="narwaniec">(However, this whole attempt to release did not come out .. I could have expected it, weakened and hungry, I did not manage Greg. I do not know how much time has passed, but I woke up in the slurry near the road. There was no sign of Greg and his crew. What to do?</string>
    <string name="ocean_twelve">Go to the sea</string>
    <string name="wejd_do_groty">Come to the dungeon</string>
    <string name="poczekaj_na_drodze">Wait near the road</string>
    <string name="ocean_swamp">(There is nothing interesting going along the coast except you found oysters and crayfish that allowed you to regain some strength. You walked until you came to the swamp.)</string>
    <string name="na_bagna">On the swamp!</string>
    <string name="gang_of_bandits">Waiting near the road, a group of passive bandits decided to have some fun with you… your corpse served as a feed for their hounds.</string>
    <string name="chose_wisely">(After a month you reached the crossroads. There are three paths, none of which look appealing. There is a sign next to the road: Choose wisely.)</string>
    <string name="skaliste_bagna">Lorem impsum2</string>
    <string name="hehe_walaka_lose">(After a hard fight you somehow managed to win … you do not know where these skills come from because you do not remember who you once were, what you did and where you were going. Unfortunately, the fight did not end without losses. You lost the left leg in which the infection entered and you feel the curse mark on yourself. An ancient curse.)</string>
    <string name="easy_exp">(Thanks to the previously acquired weapon, defeating the beast was like a walk on the rope suspended over the abyss. With eyes closed.</string>
    <string name="hidden">Hidden</string>
    <string name="v1_0">v1.0</string>
</resources>